<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book author="Read Me First" icon="icon.png" title="Welcome!" version="2.0">
	<dictionary>
		<definition word="amazing"><![CDATA[Causing great surprise or wonder; startlingly impressive]]></definition>
	</dictionary>
	<page chapter_number="1" page_number="1" type_id="1">
		<state>
			<text><![CDATA[
</br>
<p>Welcome to IMapBooks!  This IMapBook provides a guided instruction on how IMapBooks work.</p>
</br>
The first page of an IMapBook contains a story.              
Some words are highlighted on a page.  Click on a highlighted word to see its definition, like this one <span class="defWord">amazing</span>. Click again to hide the definition.
To move on to the next page, click the ">" button, below, to proceed.
			]]></text>
		</state>
	</page>
	<page chapter_number="1" page_number="2" type_id="2">
		<state>
			<text><![CDATA[
Welcome! Do you like to read? Click the words below to build your answer. To delete words, click on them.
When you finish playing the game, you will get to read more of the story.
Click on the "Books" button, above, to return to the bookshelf, or the "<" button, below, to return to previous page.
			]]></text>
			<image file_name="confufish.jpg">
			</image>
			<lexicon label="Lexicon" text="Your responses will appear here...">
				<word word="I" type_id="1"/>
				<word word="read" type_id="21"/>
				<word word="like" type_id="21"/>
				<word word="to" type_id="6"/>
				<word word="don't" type_id="21"/>
			</lexicon>
	
			<transition type_id="1" trigger="1" next_state_idx="1">
				<response type_id="1" weight="1">
					<text_input>I like to read</text_input>
					<text_output>That's terrific! I think you'll enjoy your time here.</text_output>
				</response>
				<response type_id="1" weight="1">
					<text_input>I read</text_input>
					<text_output>That's great! The more you practice reading, the better you'll get. I think you'll grow to enjoy it!</text_output>
				</response>
				<response type_id="1" weight="1">
					<text_input>I don't like to read</text_input>
					<text_output>That's okay. I think you'll still enjoy your time here!</text_output>
				</response>
				<response type_id="1" weight="1">
					<text_input>I don't read</text_input>
					<text_output>I think you might surprise yourself with how much you do read. It doesn't matter how fast or slow you go, as long as you don't stop!</text_output>
				</response>
				<text_error>I'm not sure I understand what you're saying. But I'd like to! Can you try again?</text_error>
			</transition>
		</state>
		<state score="1">
			<text><![CDATA[
I'm glad we had this little talk! I hope you enjoy your time here. Click ">" to continue.
			]]></text>
			<image file_name="confufish.jpg"/>
		</state>
	</page>
	<page chapter_number="1" page_number="3" type_id="1">
		<state>
			<text><![CDATA[
Last page...
			]]></text>
		</state>
	</page>
</book>